



# CONTACT

- GR: +30-6986597478 IT: +39-3517957838
- Thessaloniki, Greece
- Theo Stefanidis Portfolio

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Problem solving
- Decision-making
- Teamwork
- Communication skills
- Time management
- Adaptability
- Creativity
- Attention to detail
- Organizational skills
- Curiosity / Willingness to learn

#### LANGUAGES

- Greek (mother tongue)
- English (excellent)
- Italian (advanced)

# THEO STEFANIDIS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



#### **PROFILE**

Software developer with a strong passion for technology and programming. Graduated in Computer Science, with experience both in the frontend and backend, gained through participation in various projects. Known for problem-solving abilities, organized work, and a positive attitude in teamwork. Always aiming to combine technical precision with creativity to deliver effective and innovative solutions.



## WORK EXPERIENCE

Value+ srl

01/03/2024 - 01/06/2024

Milan, Italy

Front-End Developer (Internship)

- Collaborated within a development team for the creation of a web platform.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Framework, Java.



#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science 2019-2024

Aristotle University of Thessaloniki

High School Diploma 2016-2019

General Studies High School, Thessaloniki, Greece

English Degree (Michigan) 2016

Level: B2



#### TECHNOLOGIES AND SOFTWARE

- C, C++, C#, Java, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, SQL.
- Git Version Control, REST API, Node Js.
- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Autodesk Fusion360, Unity,
   Blender, IntelliJ IDEA, Visual Studio, Microsoft Office, Figma.

I invite you to visit my personal portfolio to learn more about my path, skills and projects I have completed.



#### CONTATTO

- GR: +30-6986597478 IT: +39-3517957838
- ✓ t.stefanidis24@gmail.com
- Milano, Italia
- Theo Stefanidis Portfolio

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Capacità di problem solving
- · Capacità decisionale
- Lavoro di squadra
- Capacità comunicative
- Gestione del tempo
- Adattabilità
- Creatività
- Attenzione ai dettagli
- Capacità organizzative
- Curiosità / Voglia di imparare

#### LINGUE

- Greco (madrelingua)
- Italiano (avanzato)
- Inglese (ottimo)

# THEO STEFANIDIS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



#### **PROFILO**

Sono un Software Developer con una grande passione per la tecnologia e la programmazione. Ho conseguito la laurea in Informatica e ho maturato esperienza sia nel frontend che nel backend, grazie alla partecipazione a diversi progetti. Mi contraddistingue un approccio focalizzato sulla scrittura di codice di qualità, sulla collaborazione e sul miglioramento continuo. Possiedo spiccate capacità di problem solving, la curiosità verso le nuove tecnologie e la determinazione nel contribuire allo sviluppo di soluzioni efficaci e innovative.



#### **ESPERIENZA LAVORATIVA**

Value+ srl

01/03/2024 - 01/06/2024

Front-End Developer

- Ho collaborato all'interno di un team di sviluppo per la realizzazione di una piattaforma web.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Framework, Java.



#### ISTRUZIONE

Laurea in Informatica 2019-2024

Università Aristotele, Salonicco, Grecia

Diploma di Maturità 2016-2019

Scuola Superiore Generale, Salonicco, Grecia

Certificazione di lingua inglese (Michigan) 2016

Livello: B2



## TECNOLOGIE E SOFTWARE

- C, C++, C#, Java, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, SQL.
- Git Version Control, REST API, Node Js.
- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Autodesk Fusion360, Unity, Blender, IntelliJ IDEA, Visual Studio, Microsoft Office, Figma.

Vi invito a visitare il mio portfolio personale per scoprire ulteriori dettagli su di me, la mia esperienza e i progetti a cui ho lavorato.







# ΘΕΟΔΩΡΟΣ ΣΤΕΦΑΝΙΔΗΣ

ΠΡΟΓΡΑΜΜΑΤΙΣΤΗΣ ΛΟΓΙΣΜΙΚΟΥ

## 8

#### ΠΡΟΦΙΛ

Προγραμματιστής λογισμικού με έντονο πάθος για την τεχνολογία και τον προγραμματισμό. Απόφοιτος Πληροφορικής, με εμπειρία τόσο στο frontend όσο και στο backend, η οποία αποκτήθηκε με την υλοποίηση διαφόρων project. Με χαρακτηρίζουν οι ικανότητές μου στην επίλυση προβλημάτων, η οργανωμένη μου εργασία και η ομαδικότητα. Πάντα στοχεύω στον συνδυασμό τεχνικής ακρίβειας και δημιουργικότητας, για την κατασκευή αποτελεσματικών και καινοτόμων λύσεων.



#### ΕΡΓΑΣΙΑΚΗ ΕΜΠΕΙΡΙΑ

Value+ srl

01/03/2024 - 01/06/2024

⊗ Μιλάνο, Ιταλία
Προγραμματιστής Front-End (Πρακτική)

- Ομαδική συνεργασία για την ανάπτυξη μιας διαδικτυακής πλατφόρμας.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Framework, Java.



#### ΕΚΠΑΙΔΕΥΣΗ

Πτυχίο Πληροφορικής 2019-2024

Αριστοτέλειο Πανεπιστήμιο Θεσσαλονίκης

**Απόφοιτος Λυκείου** 2016-2019

3ο ΓΕΛ Χορτιάτη, Θεσσαλονίκη, Ελλάδα

Πτυχίο Αγγλικών (Michigan) 2016

Επίπεδο: Β2

# ΤΕΧΝΟΛΟΓΙΕΣ ΚΑΙ ΛΟΓΙΣΜΙΚΑ

- C, C++, C#, Java, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, SQL.
- Git Version Control, REST API, Node Js.
- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Autodesk Fusion360, Unity,
   Blender, IntelliJ IDEA, Visual Studio, Microsoft Office, Figma.

## ΕΠΙΚΟΙΝΩΝΙΑ

- GR: +30-6986597478 IT: +39-3517957838
- ▼ t.stefanidis24@gmail.com
- Θεσσαλονίκη, Ελλάδα
- Theo Stefanidis Portfolio

## ΔΕΞΙΟΤΗΤΕΣ

- Επίλυση προβλημάτων
- Λήψη αποφάσεων
- Συνεργασία
- Δεξιότητες επικοινωνίας
- Διαχείριση χρόνου
- Προσαρμοστικότητα
- Δημιουργικότητα
- Προσοχή στη λεπτομέρεια
- Οργανωτικές δεξιότητες
- Περιέργεια / Θέληση
   συνεχούς μάθησης

#### ΓΛΩΣΣΕΣ

- Ελληνικά (μητρική)
- Αγγλικά (εξαιρετικά)
- Ιταλικά (προχωρημένα)

Σας προσκαλώ να επισκεφθείτε το προσωπικό μου portfolio για να μάθετε περισσότερα για την πορεία μου, τις δεξιότητές μου και τα έργα που έχω υλοποιήσει.